http://www.settleintoronto.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
IntroductionI/we provide a variety of products and services to the public, including but not limited to: real estate brokerage services, real estate agency services, advising with respect to real estate purchase and sale, home leasing, property management.
In the course of providing these products and services, I/we may collect, with their consent, certain personal information about our clients and persons expressing interest in obtaining more information about our services."Personal Information" means information about an identifiable individual. This may include, without limitation, the individual's name, home address, age, income, credit history or other financial information, credit card information, personal preferences and other information about his or her family. Personal Information does not include the name, title, business address or telephone number of an employee of an organization.The REALTOR™(s) that publish this Web site are members of the Canadian Real Estate Association (CREA) and subscribe to the CREA Privacy Policy.What Data Is Collected on this Web Site?No personally-identifying information is collected on this Web Site except as explicitly provided by you when requesting information. As part of the information request process, we may collect Personal Information in order to provide you with the products and services you have requested, namely: information that is required to effectively market and sell the property of sellers or lessors; to locate, assess and qualify properties for buyers; evaluate independent broker applicants, and to otherwise provide professional and competent real estate services to
clients and to ensure that you are satisfied with the products and services we have provided. I/we may also use your Personal Information to update you about our services and to offer you additional products or services.What Do You Do With My Personal Information?Please note: Personal Information collected through this Web site will not be forwarded, sold or otherwise transferred to third parties.Your Personal Information is used for three general purposes:1. To communicate with you in order to provide you with our products and services.
2. For inclusion in documentation relating to your particular real estate transaction.
3. Transactional information to monitor our level of service and report back to you to ensure your satisfaction with the provision of such services.We will only use Personal Information for the purpose that we have disclosed to you. If we want to use your information for a different purpose,we will notify you and ask for your consent first.When We are Permitted to Disclose Your Information I/we are obliged to keep your Personal Information confidential except under the following circumstances: (i) When Authorized by You (ii) When Required by Law(iii) When Permitted by Law (i) When Authorized by YouMany of the services I/we offer require us to obtain Personal Information about you in order to perform the services you have engaged us to provide. We will always obtain consent from you first, and we will never use the information for purposes other than those we have told you about.This Web Site may contain links to other Web sites, including those of its business partners. I/we are in no way responsible and cannot guarantee the content or privacy of other sites linked from this Web Site.Anonymous Information and "Cookies" This Web Site may collect anonymous information about you. This means that the information collected cannot be traced back to a specific person. For example, our Web servers may record certain information automatically when you visit this Web Site. This information is collected using "cookies" and might include the pages you visited, your IP (Internet Protocol) address and other site usage statistics. This anonymous information is used for research and analytical purposes only (like evaluating how many visitors our Web sites receive or which pages they visit most often). It does not reveal any Personal Information about you, the user. This aggregate data may be disclosed to third parties, but never with personally identifying information. "Cookies""Cookies" are small text files that contain a unique identification number that allows our computers to identify your Web browser (but not you) each time you visit one of our Web sites that uses cookies.The information helps improve the functionality of the site and enhance the navigation and security of your session. Most major Web sites use this technology and most browsers are set up to accept them. You may configure your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, and you may refuse to accept them entirely. However, if you refuse to accept cookies, you may limit the functionality that we can provide to you when you visit our site.This Web Site is operated on my/our behalf by Jumptools Inc., an Ontario Corporation operating out of Toronto, Ontario. See the Jumptools Privacy Policy.
Privacy Policy
|
Disclaimer
|
Terms and Conditions
All information displayed is believed to be accurate, but is not guaranteed and should be independently verified. No warranties or representations of any kind are made with respect to the accuracy of such information.
Not intended to solicit buyers or sellers, landlords or tenants currently under contract.
The trademarks REALTOR®, REALTORS® and the REALTOR® logo are controlled by The Canadian Real Estate Association (CREA) and identify real estate professionals who are members of CREA. The trademarks MLS®, Multiple Listing Service® and the associated logos are owned by CREA and identify the quality of services provided by real estate professionals who are members of CREA.
REALTOR® contact information provided to facilitate inquiries from consumers interested in Real Estate services. Please do not contact the website owner with unsolicited commercial offers.
Copyright© 2020 Jumptools® Inc.
Real Estate Websites for Agents and Brokers
